window.QUIZ_ARAB_NOUN = {
    "title": "Arabic Vocabulary (Arabic → English)",
    "version": 1,
    "count": 42,
    "questions": [
        {"id": 1,"question": "كِتَابٌ","options": ["An earth","A book","A Boy","A room"],"answer": "A book","answer_index": 1},
        {"id": 2,"question": "مَسْجِدٌ","options": ["A mosque","Market","Beautiful","Sun"],"answer": "A mosque","answer_index": 0},
        {"id": 3,"question": "بَيْتٌ","options": ["A sister","A house","old","Moon"],"answer": "A house","answer_index": 1},
        {"id": 4,"question": "قَلَمٌ","options": ["A pen","Bad","Tree","good"],"answer": "A pen","answer_index": 0},
        {"id": 5,"question": "جِبَالٌ","options": ["A chair","mountains","A garden","fast"],"answer": "mountains","answer_index": 1},
        {"id": 6,"question": "شَجَرَةٌ","options": ["Tree","tall","A table","dirty"],"answer": "Tree","answer_index": 0},
        {"id": 7,"question": "اِمْرَأَةٌ","options": ["Women","A brother","Cold","A student"],"answer": "Women","answer_index": 0},
        {"id": 8,"question": "كُرْسِيٌ","options": ["A chair","A mosque","Short","A father"],"answer": "A chair","answer_index": 0},
        {"id": 9,"question": "اَرْضٌ","options": ["An earth","A girl","Market","new"],"answer": "An earth","answer_index": 0},
        {"id": 10,"question": "بَابٌ","options": ["A door","A school","A room","Hot"],"answer": "A door","answer_index": 0}
    ]
}
